<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE rss PUBLIC "-//Netscape Communications//DTD RSS 0.91//EN" "http://my.netscape.com/publish/formats/rss-0.91.dtd">
<rss version="0.91">

<channel>
  <title>NetBeans News</title>
  <description>A selection of news highlights from netbeans.org, opensource IDE and application backplane</description>
  <link>http://www.netbeans.org/index.html</link>
  <language>en</language>
  <webMaster>webmaster@netbeans.org (NetBeans webmaster)</webMaster>
  <image>
    <title>NetBeans News</title>
    <url>http://www.netbeans.org/images/v5/nb-logo.gif</url>
    <link>http://www.netbeans.org/index.html</link>
    <width>110</width>
    <height>30</height>
  </image>
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 18:11:11 +0200</pubDate><!-- #TIMESTAMP# -->

    <item>
    <title>Nominate NetBeans IDE for Developer.com 2009 Product Awards!</title>
    <link>http://www.netbeans.org/community/news/index.html#1293</link>
    <description>Developer.com is now accepting nominations for its 2009 Product Awards. Vote to have your favorite developer and open-source tools become finalists for the awards.

Developer.com Nomination Page
Last year, community participation was key in the NetBeans IDE&#039;s nomination and win in three categories: Development Tool, Java Tool, and Wireless/Mobile Development Tool. Help us deliver a repeat performance for 2009 by getting NetBeans IDE on the ballot! Hurry and nominate the NetBeans IDE today!

Development Tool: NetBeans IDE

Development Utility: NetBeans Profiler

Wireless/Mobile Development Tool: NetBeans IDE (Mobility features)

Java Tool or Java Add-in of the Year: NetBeans IDE

Open Source Tool: NetBeans IDE

The nomination period ends Monday, October 13th.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Dream Projects Become Reality - NetBeans Innovators Grant Award Winners Announced!</title>
    <link>http://www.netbeans.org/community/news/index.html#1289</link>
    <description>Sun Microsystems has announced the winners of the NetBeans Innovators Grant contest, selecting 13 open source innovators to share prizes totaling $127,500. The contest was part of Sun&#039;s Open Source Community Innovation Awards Program, a multi-year program running across several open source communities with a $1 Million total prize.

For more information, read Sun&#039;s press release.

&#195;&#162;&#194;&#128;&#194;&#156;In support of Sun&#039;s commitment to free and open source software, we developed the Open Source Community Innovation Awards Program to foster innovation and recognize the most interesting initiatives within the communities worldwide,&#195;&#162;&#194;&#128;&#194;&#157; said Jiri Kovalsky, NetBeans Technical Community Manager who oversaw the NetBeans Innovators Grant program. &#195;&#162;&#194;&#128;&#194;&#156;The winners chosen demonstrated extraordinary creativity and collaboration, and their work has fueled significant growth within the NetBeans community.&#195;&#162;&#194;&#128;&#194;&#157;

Listen to an interview with Jiri Kovalsky.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>NetBeans 6.5 final l10n-kit is ready</title>
    <link>http://www.netbeans.org/community/news/index.html#1286</link>
    <description>I updated l10n-kit for NB6.5, it&#039;s from 200809151401 build and almost finalized.

http://wiki.netbeans.org/NB65L10nPlatform#section-NB65L10nPlatform-2ndL10nKit200809151401

Please pick up the latest ones. You can start translation with these files. If your team already started translation with 200808141419 kit, you need to update some files and regenerate localized files. Please refer the diff information in the wiki.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>


</channel>
</rss>

